http://www.lghcpa.com/privacy-policy/

Financial Statements
As an accounting firm, LG&H is an essential service.
For the safety of our clients and staff, our office is closed to the public and our staff is working remotely.
We can be contacted via phone and email.
All returns will be prepared and securely emailed or postal mailed to you. Since most returns are e-filed, we will provide you with a form 8879 for authorization. Please sign and email or fax it to us. If faxing or emailing is not available, we can make other arrangements for your authorization.
We want to extend all the best to you and your families in the troubling time. We are all dealing with many challenges, and will minimize the tax filing process as much as possible.
Sincerely
LG&H
More Information about the CARES act and Emergency Small Business Loans
FAQ regarding PPP loan forgiveness
PPP Forgiveness Application
Please note, your bank should send you a form
that applies to you.
Primary Navigation
Home
Tax Preparation
Business Consulting
CFO Services
Auditing
Financial Statements
About Us
LG&H
Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. This privacy policy explains how LG&H uses and protects any information that you provide us through this website, letters or e-mails from you, interviews and phone calls with you, tax returns or financial planning organizers, and financial history questionnaires. LG&H may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. This policy is effective from December 28, 2016.
A. Types of Information We Collect
We collect certain personal information about you – but only when that information is provided by you or is obtained by us with your authorization. We use that information to prepare your personal income tax returns and may also provide various tax and financial planning services to you at your request.
B. What We Do with the Information We Collect
We gather information from you to understand your needs and provide you with the best service we can. We may also use the information you give us to mail or e-mail newsletters and letters with information that may pertain to you.
C. Website
In general, the LG&H website allows visitors to use it without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. When you contact us via the website for more information, we will ask you to provide certain information by filling out and submitting an online form. This information is used solely by LG&H. We do not sell it or share it with other companies or third parties, unless compelled by law or court order to do so.
Our website has links to other websites. You will need to rely on the other websites privacy policies. We cannot be responsible for the privacy of any information you provide on other websites.
D. Parties to Whom We Disclose Information
As a general rule, we do not disclose personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone. However, to the extent permitted by law and any applicable state Code of Professional Conduct, certain nonpublic information about you may be disclosed in the following situations:
To comply with a validly issued and enforceable subpoena or summons.
In the course of a review of our firm’s practices under the authorization of a state or national licensing board, or as necessary to properly respond to an inquiry or complaint from such a licensing board of organization.
In conjunction with a prospective purchase, sale, or merger of all or part of our practice, provided that we take appropriate precautions (for example, through a written confidentiality agreement) so the prospective purchaser or merger partner does not disclose information obtained in the course of the review.
As a part of any actual or threatened legal proceedings or alternative dispute resolution proceedings either initiated by or against us, provided we disclose only the information necessary to file, pursue, or defend against the lawsuit and take reasonable precautions to ensure that the information disclosed does not become a matter of public record.
To provide information to affiliates of the firm and nonaffiliated third parties who perform services or functions for us in conjunction with our services to you, but only if we have a contractual agreement with the other party which prohibits them from disclosing or using the information other than for the purposes for which it was disclosed. (Examples of such disclosures include using an outside service bureau to process tax returns or engaging a records-retention agency to store prior year records.)
E. Confidentiality and Security of Nonpublic Personal Information
Except as otherwise described in this notice, we restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to employees of our firm and other parties who must use that information to provide services to you. Their right to further disclose and use the information is limited by the policies of our firm, applicable law, our Code of Professional Conduct, and nondisclosure agreements where appropriate.  We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws and regulations to guard your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or premature destruction.
Recent Posts
July 13, 2015
July 13, 2015
July 13, 2015
July 13, 2015
Maine Home Modification Tax Credit
12 Stillwater Ave • Bangor, ME, 04401 • 207-990-4585
8:00 – 4:30 from Memorial Day to Labor Day8:00 – 5:00 from Labor Day to Memorial Day
